[
  {
    "question": "What parameters are typically used in performance models?",
    "answers": [0, 1, 3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Arrival rate",
      "Network bandwidth",
      "Recovery time",
      "Schedule algorithm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main cost of performance modelling?",
    "answers": [1],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Compose the model",
      "Determine parameters",
      "Measure latency",
      "Measure workload"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main benefit of performance modeling?",
    "answers": [1],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Discover requirements",
      "Estimate of latency",
      "Faster system",
      "Shorter user response-time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Modeling of architecture for availability is typically carried out for determining...",
    "answers": [0, 2],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Failure rates",
      "Latency",
      "Recovery times",
      "Parallell processes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The probability that two independent servers A or B will fail is:",
    "answers": [3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["P(A) - P(B)", "P(A) / P(B)", "P(A) * P(B)", "P(A) + P(B)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The probability that both server A and server B will fail is:",
    "answers": [2],
    "exam": "2015 Kahoot 11: Modeling and Analysis",
    "options": ["P(A) - P(B)", "P(A) / P(B)", "P(A) * P(B)", "P(A) + P(B)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What analysis models exist for Usability?:",
    "answers": [2],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Conceptual framework",
      "Markov models",
      "None",
      "Real-time scheduling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What analysis models exist for Performance?:",
    "answers": [2, 3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Conceptual frameworks",
      "Component interaction metrics",
      "Queuing",
      "Real-time scheduling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What analysis models exist for Availability?:",
    "answers": [2, 3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Coupling metrics",
      "Cost models",
      "Markov models",
      "Statistical models"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What analysis models exist for Security?:",
    "answers": [3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Conceptual frameworks",
      "Component interaction metrics",
      "Cost models",
      "None"
    ]
  }
]
